totallyfuzzy.blogspot.com 2014-07-16

# InfoDesk @ totallyfuzzy.net

**Privacy Policy:**

Most clicks to outside links are being counted, for statistical and organisational purposes. We do not collect or store any additional information for those clicks.

This site uses Google Analytics, which uses a cookie that collects anonymous traffic data to be able to generate meaningful traffic statistics. (Google Analytics [Terms of Service](http://www.google.com/analytics/tos.html) \- [Google Privacy Policy)](http://www.google.com/privacy.html)

The advertising services used on this blog are very likely to use their own cookies. We do not have access to any information that might be stored in those cookies.  
You're welcome to read the terms of use of the advertising services if you want more information.

The ratings and snapshot scripts also make use of cookies.

If you should submit any personal information anywhere on this website, for submitting a blog, a review or for registration etc, that personal information, like name, email address etc, will not be collected in order to be sold or otherwise passed on to any third parties.

To protect your privacy you can use bogus information like a nickname and a webmail address.

**Privacy Policy for www.totallyfuzzy.net**

If you require any more information or have any questions about our privacy policy, please feel free to contact us by email at xmephistox@gmail.com. 

At www.totallyfuzzy.net, the privacy of our visitors is of extreme importance to us. This privacy policy document outlines the types of personal information is received and collected by www.totallyfuzzy.net and how it is used. 

**Log Files**  
Like many other Web sites, www.totallyfuzzy.net makes use of log files. The information inside the log files includes internet protocol ( IP ) addresses, type of browser, Internet Service Provider ( ISP ), date/time stamp, referring/exit pages, and number of clicks to analyze trends, administer the site, track user�s movement around the site, and gather demographic information. IP addresses, and other such information are not linked to any information that is personally identifiable. 

**Cookies and Web Beacons**

Some of our advertising partners may use cookies and web beacons on our site. Our advertising partners include Google Adsense, Commission Junction, Linkshare, . 

These third-party ad servers or ad networks use technology to the advertisements and links that appear on www.totallyfuzzy.net send directly to your browsers. They automatically receive your IP address when this occurs. Other technologies ( such as cookies, JavaScript, or Web Beacons ) may also be used by the third-party ad networks to measure the effectiveness of their advertisements and / or to personalize the advertising content that you see. 

www.totallyfuzzy.net has no access to or control over these cookies that are used by third-party advertisers. 

You should consult the respective privacy policies of these third-party ad servers for more detailed information on their practices as well as for instructions about how to opt-out of certain practices. www.totallyfuzzy.net's privacy policy does not apply to, and we cannot control the activities of, such other advertisers or web sites. 

If you wish to disable cookies, you may do so through your individual browser options. More detailed information about cookie management with specific web browsers can be found at the browsers' respective websites. 

See also [http://www.aboutcookies.org](http://www.aboutcookies.org/) or [http://www.allaboutcookies.org](http://www.allaboutcookies.org/)

**addendum: update May 19th 2009**

**Google Cookies & Privacy Policy update**

  * Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on our site.
  * Google's use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to our users based on their visit to our sites and other sites on the Internet.
  * Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the [Google ad and content network privacy policy](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html).

**addendum: update May 28th 2012**

In compliance with new EU cookie laws

  * **Cookies that are always being set on your visit here**
  * Google analytics (see above)
  * Google Adsense (see above)
  * **Cookies initiated by you (when using the site)**
  * Facebook (for comments, share and like functions)
  * Login (video site): to check whether you are logged in, to give access to some functionalities reserved for members only (playlists, favorites etc)
  * User interface browse mode (video site)
  * Youtube (video site) when watching videos

Original : October 5th 2008

Updated: May 19th 2009

Last update: May 28th 2012
